<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Nyanyanya!</title>
    <link>http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Nyanyanya!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Products</title>
      <link>http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/products/</guid>
      <description>SSRN IDEAS/PePEc Google Scholar
 Wendy Li, Makoto Nirei, Kazufumi Yamana, Creative Destruction in Organizational Capital: Evidence from the Online Platform Economy in Japan and the United States
 Wendy Li, Makoto Nirei, Kazufumi Yamana, Value of Data: There&amp;rsquo;s No Such Thing As A Free Lunch in the Digital Economy
 Shuhei Aoki, Makoto Nirei, Kazufumi Yamana, Risk-Taking, Inequality and Output in the Long-Run, BOJ Working Paper Series, No.18-E4, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offshoots</title>
      <link>http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/offshoots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/offshoots/</guid>
      <description> Yamana, Kazufumi, Empirical Studies of the Digital Economy: Survey, Statistics (Japanese), Nov 2018 Yamana, Kazufumi. et al., Airbnb in Japan, The studies in economics and trade (Japanese), Mar 2018 Yamana, Kazufumi, What is the Evidence-Based Policy Making?, Finance (Japanese), Aug 2017 Kazufumi Yamana and Makoto Nirei, A quantitative study on the sharing economy, Bulletin report (Japanese), Mar 2017  Summary (Japanese) Workshop (Japanese)  Yamana, Kazufumi, Recent trends: asset pricing, Finance (Japanese), Feb 2016  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nekonomist.github.io/projects/talks/</guid>
      <description>Conferences 2019 AEA (Jan)
2018 IMFSF(Nov), IPSDM(Oct), IISES (Sep), IARIW (Aug)
2017 CAED (Sep), JEA (Sep), KLEMS (July), JSS (Mar), ASSA (Jan)
2016 JEA (Jun), JSS (Mar)
2015 JEA (May)
2014 JEA (Oct), HitU (Mar)
Others 2016 MOF (Nov), DSGEWS (Jul), JCER (Jan), KyotoU (Jan)
2014 SWET (Aug)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>